Guide to the Associate University Librarian for Technical Services, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Administrative records, 1985-1993; Accession 1995-A-018
  - NOTIS (Box 4)
    - Cost Information Sheet (Box 5)
    - CPU Pricing (Box 5)
    - Database Content (Box 5)
    - Database Load (Box 5)
    - Database Load - NOTIS (Box 5)
    - Database Load - RLIN (Box 5)
    - Database Load - UTLAS (Box 5)
    - Database Load - Yale (Box 5)
    - Database Maintenance (Box 5)
    - Demos (Box 5)
    - Description of Candidate Systems (Box 5)
    - Developments (Box 5)
    - Divinity Library (Box 5)
    - Documentation (Box 5)
    - Documentation Specialist (Box 5)
    - Downloading to Micros (Box 5)
    - Electrical (Box 5)
    - Enhancements (Box 5)
    - Ergonomics (Box 5)
    - Facilities Management (Box 5)
    - Fiscal Support Group (Box 5)
    - Focus Group on System Architecture (Box 5)
    - Forestry Library (Box 5)
    - Funding agreement (Box 5)
    - GEAC Database Conversion (Box 5)
    - GEAC Database Load (Box 5)
    - Glossary (Box 5)
    - Government Documents (Box 5)
    - GTO (Box 5)
    - Handicapped Access (Box 5)
    - Hardware (Box 5)
    - Harvard (Box 5)
    - Helpscreens (Box 5)
    - Index Redesign (Box 5)
    - Installation (Box 5)
    - Keyword (Box 5)
    - Law Library (Box 5)
    - LC Marc Tapes (Box 5)
    - Local Maintenance (Box 5)
    - Location Codes (Box 5)
    - LSP (Box 5)
    - MATPS Conversion (Box 5)
    - MDAS (Box 5)
    - Medical Library (Box 5)
    - Multiple Databases (Box 5)
    - Name (Box 6)
    - Name - Contest Entries (Box 6)
    - Nave (Box 6)
    - OCG (ORBIS COORDINATING GROUP) (Box 6)
    - OPAC (Box 6)
    - OPAC (patron Requests) (Box 6)
    - Planning (Box 6)
    - Presentations (Box 6)
    - Project Description - Originals (Box 6)
    - Provostls Ad Hoc Committee (Box 6)
    - Publicity (Box 6)
    - Quik Requests (Box 6)
    - Relationships wilh office (Box 6)
    - Release 5.0 (Box 6)
    - Remote Access (Box 6)
    - RLG Discussion Group (Box 6)
    - Retrospective Conversion (Box 6)
    - Retrospective Conversion Task Force (Box 6)
    - Review 190 (Box 6)
    - Review 193 (Box 6)
    - Review Group (Box 6)
    - RLIN Lrs (Box 6)
    - RLIN Transaction Tapes (Box 6)
    - RLIN Updating (Box 6)
    - RLIN Workflow (Box 6)
    - Security (Box 6)
    - Serials (Box 6)
    - Serials Conversion (Box 6)
    - Serials - Curators (Box 6)
    - Serials Working Group (Box 6)
    - Shelflisting (Box 6)
    - Sign On (Box 6)
    - Staffmg (Box 6)
    - Startup (Box 6)
    - Statistics (Box 6)
    - System Architecture (Box 6)
    - System Architecture Processing Unit Issue (Box 6)
    - System Availability (Box 6)
    - System News (Box 6)
    - Task Force Organizations (Box 6)
    - Task List (Box 6)
    - Tech Link (Box 6)
    - Telecommunications (Box 6)
    - NOrIS Test System (Box 6)
    - Timeline (Box 6)
    - Training (Box 6)
    - Training Task Force (Box 6)
    - University of Iowa (Box 6)
    - Use Statistics (Box 6)
    - User Support (Box 6)
    - Users Group (Box 6)
    - Vendor Access (Box 6)
    - Vernacular Issues (Box 6)
    - Yale/IBM Project (Box 6)
    - YCC Facilities Management (Box 6)
    - YUL Proposal (Box 6)
  - NREN (Box 6)
  - ONLINE CATALOGING (Box 6)
  - OPTICAL DISK ADVISORY COMMITTEE (Box 6)
  - OPTIRAM - PRINCETON PROJECT (Box 6)
  - ORBIS - PUBLICITY (Box 6)
  - ORGANIZATIONAL CHANGE (Box 6)
  - ORGANIZATIONAL DESIGN and DEVELOPMENT (Box 6)
  - OVERTIME (Box 6)
  - PAMPHLETS (Box 6)
  - PARITlME WORK (Box 6)
  - PATRON REQUEST (Box 6)
  - PEABODY MUSEUM (Box 6)
  - PERFORMANCE EXPECTATIONS (Box 6)
  - PERFORMANCE EXPECTATIONS- TASK FORCE ON (Box 6)
  - PERMANENT PAPER TASK FORCE (Box 6)
  - PRODUCTIVITY (Box 7)
  - PROJECT ELI (Box 7)
  - PROMOTION AND MERIT REVIEW (Box 7)
  - PRR (Box 7)
  - RETIREMENT (Box 7)
  - RLIN /OCLC STEERING COMMITIEE (Box 7)
  - SAM (SYSTEM AUTOMATION :MEMO) (Box 7)
  - SCANNING (Box 7)
  - SCHOLARLY INFORMATION SYSTEMS WORKING GROUP (Box 7)
  - SCHOLARIS INFORMATION WORK STATION (Box 7)
  - SCOPA (Box 7)
  - SECURITY (Box 7)
  - SERIAL CATALOG (Box 7)
  - SERIALS (Box 7)
    - Periodicals List Project (Box 7)
    - Pricing (Box 7)
    - Serials Task Force Recommendation (Box 7)
    - Statistics (Box 7)
  - SET PROCESSING (Box 7)
  - SHARED CATALOGING (Box 7)
  - SLAVIC and EAST EUROPEAN COLLECTION (Box 7)
  - SOFTWARE ACQUISITION (TASK FORCE) (Box 7)
  - SOUTHEAST ASIA COLLECTION (Box 7)
    - Luce Proposal (Box 7)
  - SPACE PLANNING (Box 7)
  - STAFF DEVELOPMENT (Box 7)
  - STAFF RECOGNITION PROGRAM (Box 7)
  - STANDARDS FOR UNIVERSITY LIBRARIES (Box 7)
  - STAT LAB (Box 7)
  - STRATEGIC PLANNING - OTHER UNIVERSITIES (Box 7)
  - STUDENT WORKERS (Box 7)
  - SUBJECT CATALOG (Box 7)
  - SYSTEMS OFFICE I (Box 7)
  - SYSTEMS OFFICE II (Box 7)
    - Annual Report, 1982-1983 (Box 7)
  - TASCH PROJECT (Box 7)
  - TECHNICAL SERVICES (Box 7)
    - Proposed Staff Changes (Box 7)
    - Research Libraries Survey (Box 7)
  - TELECONFERENCING (Box 7)
  - TELEPHONES I (Box 7)
  - TITLE II-C (Box 7)
  - TRAINING (Box 7)
    - Microcomputer (Box 7)
    - Processing Services (Box 7)
    - Team Leaders (Box 7)
    - Training Needs Group (Box 7)
  - TRAVEL BUDGET (Box 7)
    - FY 89/90 (Box 7)
    - FY 90/91 (Box 7)
    - FY91 (Box 7)
    - FY92 (Box 7)
  - TRAVEL REGULATIONS (Box 7)
  - TURNER (Box 7)
  - UMI (Box 7)
  - UNION CONTRACT (Box 7)
    - 1985 (Box 7)
    - 1988 (Box 7)
    - 1992 (Box 7)
  - UNION LITERATORE (Box 7)
  - UNION RELANOTIS (Box 7)
  - UNITED STATES NEWSPAPER PROJECT (Box 8)
  - UNIVERSITY COUNCIL COMMITIEE ON THE LIBRARY (Box 8)
  - UTLAS (Box 8)
  - VIDEO ARCIDVES FOR HOLOCAUST TESTIMONIES (Box 8)
  - WEI-TO (Box 8)
  - WHOLE DISCIPLINE PROJECfS (Box 8)
  - WITHDRAWAL POLICY (Box 8)
  - WORKERS COMPENSATION (Box 8)
  - WORKFLOW PROJECT (Box 8)
  - WORKSTATION PROJECT (Box 8)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY
    - ACADEMlC PLAN (Box 8)
    - BUDGET (Box 8)
    - EXTREME WEATHER POLICY (Box 8)
    - FINANCIAL INFORMATION SYSTEMS STEERING COMM. (Box 8)
    - FINANCIAL REPORT (Box 8)
    - RESTRUCTURING COMMITIEE (Box 8)
    - STATISTICS (Box 8)
  - YALE UNIVERSITY LIBRARY
    - ANNUAL REPORT (Box 8)
    - AUTOMATION (Box 8)
    - CALENDAR (Box 8)
    - FIVE YEAR PLAN (Box 8)
    - ORGANIZATION (Box 8)
    - PRIORITY ACTION PLANS 93/94 (Box 8)
    - PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT GRANTS (Box 8)
    - SPACE PLANNING (Box 8)
    - STAFFING (Box 8)
    - STATISTICS (Box 8)
    - SML RENOVANOTIONS (Box 8)
    - STRATEGIC PLANNING (Box 8)
    - STUDENTWORKERS (Box 8)
    - WORKING MODEL (Box 8)
  - YELLOW PAGES (Box 8)
  - BASELINE DATA GATHERING (Box 8)
  - TECHNICAL SERVICES REORGANIZATION
    - BASELINE DATA GATHERING - JOB SATISFACTION SURVEY (Box 9)
    - BUDGET STRUCfURE (Box 9)
    - DATA BASE MAINTENANCE TEAM (Box 9)
    - DOWNLOADING TO MICROS (Box 9)
    - EDUCATION PROGRAM (Box 9)
    - EVALUATION (Box 9)
    - GENERAL MEMOS (Box 9)
    - GLASER REVIEW (Box 9)
    - HACKMAN (Box 9)
    - HEWIIT -REVIEW (Box 9)
    - JOB DESCRIPTIONS (Box 9)
    - MATERIALS MANAGEMENT (Box 9)
    - PAINTING (Box 9)
    - PHILOSOPHIES (REORG) (Box 9)
    - PLAN - Oct. 29, 1987 (Proposal) (Box 9)
    - PLAN - Oct. 29, 1987 (Proposal) - Comments (Box 9)
    - PLAN - May 4, 1988 (First Draft) (Box 9)
    - PLAN - May 4, 1988 (First Draft) - Comments (Box 9)
    - PLAN - June 17, 1988 (Final Draft) (Box 9)
    - PLAN - June 17, 1988 (Final Draft) - Comments (Box 9)
    - PLAN - June 24,1988 (Final Version) (Box 9)
    - PLAN REVISION (Box 9)
    - PRESENTANOTIS I (Box 9)
    - PRESENTATIONS II (Box 9)
    - PRESS RELEASES (Box 9)
    - PUBLIC RELATIONS (Box 9)
    - PUBLICIIT (Box 9)
    - READING MATERIALS I (Box 9)
    - READING MATERIALS II (Box 9)
    - REORG REVIEW TASK GROUP (Box 9)
    - REORGANIZAnONCOUNCIL (Box 9)
    - REORGANIZATION REVIEW TASK FORCE (Box 9)
    - REVIEW - JUNE 1989 (Box 9)
    - REVIEW - 1990 (Box 9)
    - REVIEW - 2/90 (Box 9)
    - REVIEW TASK FORCE (Box 9)
    - SERIALS COUNCIL (Box 9)
    - SPACE PLANNING (Box 9)
    - STAFF RECOGNITION PROGRAM - STAFFING (Box 9)
    - SUBGROUP ON JOB DESCRIPTIONS (Box 9)
    - SUBGROUP ON PUBLIC RELATIONS (Box 10)
    - TASKFORCE (Box 10)
    - TASK FORCE (REPORT OF) (Box 10)
    - TEAM LEADERS (Box 10)
    - TEAMS (Box 10)
      - Tasks (Box 10)
    - TRAINING (Box 10)
      - CLR Grant (Box 10)
      - Hackman (Training) (Box 10)
      - Organizational Design and Development (Box 10)
      - Team LeadersI (Box 10)
      - Team Leaders IT (Box 10)
    - WORKFLOW (Box 10)
  - RLG /RLIN
    - RLIN - Academic Software Catalog Project (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Activity Estimates (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Arabic Enhancements (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Aspen (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Authorities (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Bibliographic Statistical Analysis Reports (Box 10)
    - RLIN - BibTech (Box 10)
    - RLIN - BibTech Fall 1988 (Box 10)
    - RLlN- BibTcch Spring '90 (Box 10)
    - RLG /RLIN BibTech Steering Commiuee (Box 10)
    - RLG BibTech Task Force on Cooperative Cataloging (Box 10)
    - RLG Board of Governors (Box 10)
    - RLIN Budget (Yale) (Box 10)
    - RLIN Budget (Yale) FY 89/90 (Box 10)
    - RLIN Budget (Yale) FY 90191 (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Budget (Yale) FY 91192 (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1986 (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1987 (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1988 (Box 10)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1989 (Box 11)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1990 (Box 11)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1991 (Box 11)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1992 (Box 11)
    - RLIN - Cataloging Status 1993 (Box 11)
    - RLG Citadel (Box 11)
    - RLIN Class (Box 11)
    - RLG CMDC (Box 11)
    - RLG Commission on Technical Processing (Box 11)
    - RLG Eureka (Box 11)
    - RLIN Hardware (Box 11)
    - RLIN Hebrew Enhancements (Box 11)
    - RLIN Inion (Box 11)
    - RLIN Interlibrary Loan (Box 11)
    - RLIN Internal Response Time Limits (Box 11)
    - RLIN Internet (Box 11)
    - RLIN Library Systems Officers Forum (Box 11)
    - RLG Listservs (Box 11)
    - RLIN Loading Member Data (Box 11)
    - RLIN LSP (Box 11)
    - RLIN Local Systems (Box 11)
    - RLG Mail System (Box 11)
    - RLIN Maintenance Charges (Box 11)
    - RLIN Marc Import Record (Box 11)
    - RLG Member Activity Summary I (Box 11)
    - RLG Member Activity Summary II (Box 11)
    - RLG Mid-decade Planning Group (Box 11)
    - RLIN Needs Assessment Survey (Box 11)
    - RLIN Network (Box 11)
    - RLG News (Box 11)
    - RLG OCLC (Box 11)
    - RLG Operations Update (Box 11)
    - RLIN Organization (Box 11)
    - RLIN Pass (Box 11)
    - RLIN Perfonnance (Box 11)
    - RLG Preservation Committee (Box 11)
    - RLG Press Release (Box 11)
    - RLG Prima (Box 12)
    - RLG Programs Advisory Group (Box 12)
    - RLIN Rates (Box 12)
    - RLG RLIN Record Task Force (Box 12)
    - RLIN Retrospective Conversion (Box 12)
    - RLG '92 (Box 12)
    - RLIN Searching Activity (Box 12)
    - RLG Special Committee (Box 12)
    - RLG Steering Committee (Box 12)
    - RLG Strategic Directions (Box 12)
    - RLIN Tapes (Box 12)
    - RLIN Telenet (Box 12)
    - RLIN Terminals (Box 12)
    - RLIN Unlimited Searching (Box 12)
    - RLIN User Satisfaction Survey (Box 12)
    - RLG Yale Representatives (Box 12)
- Integrated Technical Services and Systems records of Donald Waters, 1986-1994; Accession 1995-A-067a
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2029
  - Acquisitions (Box 1)
    - Backlogs (Box 1)
  - Binding, plating and labeling (Box 1)
    - Blanket Orders (Box 1)
    - Deposit Accounts (Box 1)
    - Documentation (Box 1)
    - Elsevier (Box 1)
    - Exchanges (Box 1)
    - Fiscai Support Team (Box 1)
    - Foreign Vendor Payments (Box 1)
    - Procedures (Box 1)
    - Request for Proposal, 1992 (Box 1)
    - Sale of Duplicates (Box 1)
    - Sale of Duplicates, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Serials (Box 1)
    - Subscriptions (Box 1)
    - Transfer (Box 1)
    - Vendor Files (Box 1)
  - African Collection (Box 1)
  - American Antiquarian Society - Evans Data (Box 1)
  - American Library Association (Box 1)
    - Jul 1988 (Box 1)
    - Jan 1990 (Box 1)
    - Jan 1991 (Box 1)
    - Jan 1992 (Box 1)
    - Jun1992 (Box 1)
    - Jun1993 (Box 1)
      - Preconference Talk - 1 (Box 1)
      - Preconference Talk - 2 (Box 1)
    - Feb 1994 (Box 1)
    - Imaging Talk (Box 1)
  - Apple Corporation-Proposal (Box 1)
  - Apple Library of Tomorrow (Box 1)
  - Arts of the Book (Box 1)
  - ASIS (Box 1)
    - Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 1)
    - Conference, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Association of Research Libraries (ARL) (Box 1)
    - Office of Management Services (OMS) (Box 1)
      - Resource Management Retreat (Box 1)
  - Attendance Reports (Box 1)
  - Automation SUlVeys (Box 1)
  - Babylonian Collection (Box 1)
  - Beinecke Library (Box 1)
  - BNA-Automation (Box 1)
  - Business Office (Box 1)
    - Business Managers Meeting (Box 1)
    - Wages (Box 1)
  - CARL (Box 1)
  - Carnegie Mellon (Box 1)
  - Cataloging (Box 2)
    - Activity Reports (Box 2)
    - Authority Control (Box 2)
  - Character Set Issues (Box 2)
    - ASIS Presentation (Box 2)
    - LITA (Box 2)
  - Chemistry Lab (Box 2)
  - Circulation (Box 2)
    - Special Charges (Box 2)
  - CIMTECH (Box 2)
  - Coalition for Networked Infonnation (Box 2)
    - Fall 1991 (Box 2)
    - Fall 1992 (Box 2)
    - Spring 1992 (Box 2)
    - Fall 1993 (Box 2)
    - Mar 1993 (Box 2)
  - Collection Development Reports (Box 2)
  - Common Command Language (Box 2)
  - Communications (Box 2)
    - Appletalk Network (Box 2)
    - Departmental LAN Committee (Box 2)
      - Exemplar Study (Box 2)
      - Existing LANS (Box 2)
      - Final Report I (Box 2)
      - Final Report II (Box 2)
      - General Survey (Box 2)
      - Meeting Notes (Box 2)
      - Residential Colleges (Box 2)
    - Local Area Networks (LAN) (Box 2)
      - Carnegie Mellon University (Box 2)
      - Clippings (Box 2)
      - University of Michigan (Box 2)
    - University Networking Committee (Box 2)
      - 1987-1988 (Box 2)
      - Electronic Mail Subcommittee (Box 2)
      - Network Management Subcommittee (Box 2)
      - Wiring Subcommittee (Box 2)
  - Communications Department (Box 2)
  - Current Clinical Trials (Box 2)
  - Current Contents (Box 2)
  - Dartmouth College (Box 2)
  - Educom (Box 2)
    - 1992 (Box 2)
    - 1992 (Box 2)
    - 1993 (Box 2)
    - 1994 (Box 2)
    - Fall 1990 (Box 2)
  - Electronic Journals (Box 2)
  - Enterprise Statistics (Box 2)
  - Environmental Infonnation (Box 2)
  - Equipment Inventories (Box 2)
  - Ergonomics (Box 2)
  - Facsimile (Box 2)
  - Faxon Institute Conference (Box 2)
  - Financial Administrators Group (Box 3)
  - Flood Control (Box 3)
  - Forestry School - Orbis (Box 3)
  - Friends of the New Haven Public Library - Talk, 1993 June (Box 3)
  - GEAC (Box 3)
  - Grants and Contracts (Box 3)
  - Harvard Institute" (Box 3)
  - Institution for Social and Policy Studies (Box 3)
  - Integration: What Is It? (Box 3)
  - Interlibrary Loan (Box 3)
  - IBM-SLSS (Box 3)
  - Internet Sources (Box 3)
  - Joumal of Library Administration (Box 3)
  - Leadership in Higher Education (Box 3)
  - Lewis Walpole Library (Box 3)
  - Legi-slate (Box 3)
  - Library Catalogs (Box 3)
  - Library Lists (Box 3)
  - Library of Congress (Box 3)
    - Catalog Distribution: MARC Tapes (Box 3)
    - Network Advisory Committee (Box 3)
    - Networks for Networkers (Box 3)
    - Workshop on Electronic Texts (Box 3)
  - Linked Systems Project (Box 3)
  - Listservs I (Box 3)
  - Listservs II (Box 3)
  - LITA (Box 3)
    - Conference, 1992 (Box 3)
    - Meeting, 1988 October (Box 3)
    - Talk, 1992 September (Box 3)
  - Machine Readable Data Files (Box 3)
  - Machine Upgrade, 1993 (Box 3)
  - MARC Record Tools (Box 3)
  - MATPS (Box 3)
    - Conversion (Box 3)
    - Equipment, IBM Series I (Box 3)
    - Fund Register (Box 3)
    - Sycor Conversion (Box 3)
    - Sycor Replacement (Box 3)
    - Use Under Orbis (Box 3)
    - YCC Support (Box 3)
  - Microform Review (Box 3)
  - Microsoft (Box 3)
  - Visit (Box 3)
  - Music Library (Box 3)
  - National Archives (Box 3)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 3)
  - National NET 90 (Box 3)
  - National NET 94 (Box 3)
  - National Science Foundation - Networking (Box 3)
  - NENUG-L, Northeast NOTIS Users Group (Box 3)
  - Northwestern OPAC (Box 3)
  - NOTIS (Box 3)
    - Customer Profiles, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Documentation Distribution List (Box 4)
    - Enhancement Ballot, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Enhancement Survey, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
    - Enhancements, 1992 July - August (Box 4)
    - Focus Group on Systems Architecture (Box 4)
    - GTO (Box 4)
    - Health Science Users Group (Box 4)
    - OTIS (Box 4)
    - Quik Reports (Box 4)
    - Serials Control 5.l (Box 4)
  - NREN (Box 4)
  - Numismatics (Box 4)
  - Optiram (Box 4)
  - ORBIS (Box 4)
    - Applications Implementation Task Force (Box 4)
    - AITF (Box 4)
    - Articles (Box 4)
    - Automation Steering Committee (Box 4)
    - Beta Test (Box 4)
      - Announcements (Box 4)
      - Evaluations (Box 4)
      - General (Box 4)
    - Bindery Support (Box 4)
    - Card Catalog Use (Box 4)
    - Card Production (Box 4)
    - Character Set Representation (Box 4)
    - Communication (Box 4)
    - Course Reserves (Box 4)
    - CRLtapes (Box 4)
    - Database Load (Box 4)
      - ARL-NOTIS (Box 4)
      - BNA (Box 4)
      - Criteria (Box 4)
      - GEAC-NOTIS (Box 4)
      - Procedure (Box 4)
      - RLIN-NOTIS (Box 4)
        - Authority Control (Box 4)
        - Conversion (Box 4)
        - Overlay (Box 4)
        - Production (Box 4)
        - Snapshot Tape 1 (Box 4)
        - Snapshot Tape 2 (Box 4)
        - Specifications (Box 4)
        - Subcontractors (Box 4)
    - Deposit Accounts (Box 4)
    - Desiderata Files (Box 4)
    - Documentation (Box 4)
      - Core (Box 4)
      - Crib Sheets (Box 4)
      - Fact Sheet (Box 4)
      - Glossary (Box 4)
      - Help Screens (Box 4)
      - Sign-on (Box 4)
    - Fiscal Year Rollover (Box 4)
    - Front End Software - IBM (Box 4)
    - Generic Transfer and Overlay (GTO) (Box 4)
    - GPO File (Box 4)
    - Index Structure (Box 4)
    - Invoice Processing (Box 4)
    - Keyword-Boolean (Box 4)
    - Law Libnuy (Box 4)
    - LC Resource File (Box 4)
    - Location Codes (Box 4)
    - Management Reports (Box 4)
    - NOTIS 5.0 Implementation (Box 4)
    - NOTIS 5.1 Implementation (Box 4)
    - NOTIS-RLIN Tapeout Project - Beta Test Plan Requirements (Box 4)
    - OPAC Predictions (Box 4)
    - OPAC Statistics (Box 4)
    - Operations: Problems and Change (Box 4)
    - Overview (Box 4)
    - Patron Request Procedures (Box 4)
    - Perfonnance (Box 4)
    - Planning Retreat, 1990 July 31 (Box 4)
    - Press Release (Box 4)
    - Processing Units (Box 4)
    - Project Planning (Box 4)
    - Public Relations Task Force (Box 4)
    - Record Structure (Box 4)
    - Remote Access (Box 4)
      - General (Box 4)
      - User Survey (Box 4)
    - Reports (Box 4)
    - Residential College Support (Box 4)
    - RLG-NOTIS Users Group (Box 4)
    - RLIN Tape Output Program (Box 4)
    - Search Statistics (Box 4)
    - Selector Review (Box 4)
    - Serials Control (Box 4)
    - Set Processing (Box 4)
    - 7171 Room (Box 4)
    - Smart Bar Codes (Box 4)
    - Status Tracking (Box 4)
    - SMLNave (Box 4)
    - Syne Sort (Box 4)
    - Systems Automation Memo (SAM) (Box 4)
    - System Messages (Box 4)
    - System Reliability (Box 4)
    - Tape Output Program (Box 4)
    - Tenninal Configurations (Box 4)
      - Electrical Work (Box 4)
      - Furniture (Box 4)
      - Furniture - SML Nave (Box 4)
      - Handicapped Access (Box 4)
    - Tenninal Equipment (Box 4)
      - 3163 Replacement (Box 4)
      - Bar Code Scanners (Box 4)
      - IBM 3151 (Box 5)
      - Survey of Users (Box 5)
    - Tenninal Planning (Box 5)
    - Timeline (Box 5)
    - Training Task Force (Box 5)
      - Agenda and minutes (Box 5)
      - Charge (Box 5)
      - Experience questionnaires (Box 5)
      - External contacts (Box 5)
      - Glossary (Box 5)
      - Hands on demonstrations (Box 5)
      - Introduction to NOTIS, Spring 1987 (Box 5)
      - Introduction to ORBIS (Box 5)
      - MARC overview (Box 5)
      - NOTIS training syllabus (Box 5)
      - Organizational change workshops (Box 5)
      - Planning documents (Box 5)
      - Pre-installation training (Box 5)
      - Question and answer sessions (Box 5)
      - Testing framework (Box 5)
      - Training team (Box 5)
      - Train the trainers (Box 5)
    - Transaction Reports (Box 5)
    - Vendors (Box 5)
    - VTILS (Box 5)
    - Volume Holdings Conversion (Box 5)
    - Walker Interface (Box 5)
  - Organizational Change (Box 5)
  - Policy Advisory and Communications Council (PACC) (Box 5)
    - Cost Reduction Analysis (Box 5)
    - Fall, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Minutes (Box 5)
    - RLG Review, 1988 March (Box 5)
  - Preservation (Box 5)
    - Biblioteca Nazionale Italiana (Box 5)
    - GEAC Usage for Piece Control (Box 5)
    - Gelernter disaster (Box 5)
  - Princeton University (Box 5)
  - Procurement (Box 5)
  - Promotion Review Committee (Box 5)
  - Record Management (Box 5)
  - Reference Department (Box 5)
  - Research Libraries Group (RLG) (Box 5)
    - Annual Meeting, 1992 June (Box 5)
    - AMIS (Box 5)
    - Board of Governors (Box 5)
    - Cataloger's Workstation (Box 5)
    - Central Staff Organization (Box 5)
    - Document Transmission Workstation (Box 5)
    - Linked Systems Project (Box 5)
    - Local Systems and RLG (Box 5)
    - Local Systems Officers Forum (Box 5)
    - Local Systems Planning Committee Correspondence, 1988 January (Box 5)
      - Long Range Planning Subcommittee Report (Box 6)
      - Meeting 6/86 (Box 6)
      - Meeting 10/86 (Box 6)
      - Meeting 1/87 (Box 6)
      - Meetingll/87 (Box 6)
      - Meeting 10/88 (Box 6)
      - Meeting with Bibtech, 1987 June (Box 6)
      - Steering Committee, 1989 July (Box 6)
        - Meeting, 1989 October (Box 6)
    - RLIN (Box 6)
      - LI Structure, Proposed Change (Box 6)
      - MARC Import Record Specifications (Box 6)
      - MARC Record Description (Box 6)
      - Network (Box 6)
      - PC Terminals (Box 6)
      - Site Visit, 1990 September (Box 6)
      - System (Box 6)
  - Salary Levels (Box 6)
  - SAS (Box 6)
  - SCOPA (Box 6)
    - Annual Report, 1988-1989 (Box 6)
  - Set Processing (Box 6)
    - Chadwyck-Healey (Box 6)
  - Systems Office (Box 6)
    - Action Plans, 1991-1993 (Box 6)
    - Bibliography (Box 6)
    - Budget (Box 6)
    - Clippings (Box 6)
    - Contacts (Box 6)
    - Data Administration (Box 6)
    - Equipment Requests (Box 6)
      - 1989 (Box 6)
      - 1990 (Box 6)
      - 1991 (Box 6)
    - Executive Group (Box 6)
    - General (Box 6)
    - Generic Job Descriptions (Box 6)
    - Grant Applications (Box 6)
    - Hotline (Box 6)
    - Meeting Agendas (Box 6)
    - Microcomputer Support (Box 6)
    - Move (Box 6)
    - Organization (Box 6)
    - Planning (Box 6)
      - Jan-92 (Box 6)
    - Planning and Goal Setting, 1990 March (Box 6)
    - Programming Team (Box 6)
    - Projects (Box 6)
      - PACC Presentation, 1991 February (Box 6)
    - Publications Received (Box 6)
    - Space (Box 6)
    - Travel Policy (Box 6)
    - Travel Requests (Box 6)
    - Workstation Team (Box 7)
  - TCI (Box 7)
  - Technical Services (Box 7)
    - Team Leader Meetings (Box 7)
    - Technical Support for Groups, Grant (Box 7)
  - Teleconferencing (Box 7)
  - Telephone Services (Box 7)
  - Telnet (Box 7)
  - Teradata (Box 7)
    - Access Project (Box 7)
  - Travel Requests, 1988-1990 (Box 7)
  - Travel Requests, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
  - Vendor Review (Box 7)
  - Video Workstation (Box 7)
  - Voicemail (Box 7)
  - WAIS (Box 7)
  - WHO/Collaborating Center (Box 7)
    - HAPINS (Box 7)
    - Proposals (Box 7)
  - Yale University (Box 7)